So it's not weird, y'all, at all that all of a sudden there's a Black Panther chapter in Philly that is posting videos like every day with a dude that none of us have ever worked with before.
That's not weird, y'all.
It's not weird, y'all, that the algorithm is just pushing that through.
So it's not weird, y'all, that they're showing the faces of the individuals who are recruits and who are working with them.
Meanwhile, the people they're fighting against are not showing their faces.
That's not odd, y'all.
It's not odd, y'all, that when you look in the comments, it's a bunch of people commenting who have never worked with them before, who have never said anything about them before.
Or, like, they're praising them because, of course, we all want inspiration and we all want to feel like, okay, folks are stepping up and protecting.
But, like, if someone can show me, if someone can show me track record, I'll shut up.
For real, I will.
I just, I can't see, I can't, I don't see track record.
Like, to me, it don't look like the beginning of my movement.
It looks like a, it looks like a marketing rollout for an album.
That, like, that's what it looks like to me from my experience in entertainment.
I don't, I'm just, like, the constant psyop is something that I'm always cognizant of.
And when I'm seeing that, it's ringing bells, like penitentiary cells.
Like, I just, so, you know, feel free to, of course, correct me.
I'm just speaking honestly about my spidey sensory.
And I don't like it.
Now, were these questions to be answered, only one of two things can happen.
Either one, we see that, okay, this is some phony baloney.
Or two, we see that, okay, there's something real going on that more people can get involved with.
So, there's really no short side to this inquiry.
Power to the people.
All slaves, and you love it.